{
    "id": "6fb35ee516c7415199e2409accd93819",
    "title": "Prepositions After Verbs, Nouns And Adjectives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am interested ...................... learning to fly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "56bf15905c514c2da0bf61f29f2a3213"
        },
        {
            "question": "John's criticism ......................... the plan made him unpopular.",
            "description": "The noun criticism needs a preposition to connect it to a noun or ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "22c14093765246d190fcb4ffd6d88683"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has always been critical ......................... me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2c0f567d61b5406eb63146be1d5960f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I resent .................................. on weekends.",
            "description": "Some verbs can be followed by nouns or ing forms with no preposition. Resent is one of them. ",
            "answers": [
                "working",
                "for working",
                "about working"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ece8089fd24545329ae6ecf3e414e9bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "My resentment .................................. working on holidays made me unpopular with my boss.",
            "description": "Resentment is followed by of. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9244f1e93f4946f09d67880ad3f6df0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel resentful ......................... working on Sundays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0760f7cc14534966adf0da82a50ca6f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ignored our worries ........................... her health.",
            "description": "We worry about something. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "about",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4372e096020747bbb1cefdc718077ec9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can only sympathize ......................... you.",
            "description": "We sympathize with people. We do not sympathize for or at them. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "32862cc0ff1c40239714aca9f4ea68eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel great sympathy ........................ her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "for",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f748960072e479ebc331a09cd361b7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel sympathetic ............................. the poor.",
            "description": "Sympathetic is followed by towards. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "at",
                "towards"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2d16fc364c1b46fcb44829f66de96048"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had given up hope ........................ seeing her again.",
            "description": "Hope is followed by of + noun/ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "93dbb7b64a4140ea962ee5683e05fc6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ....................... the station last night.",
            "description": "A preposition is usually necessary before an expression of place. ",
            "answers": [
                "arrived",
                "arrived at",
                "arrived to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fca6cbd9b2134f149588ccf8f28ec15b"
        }
    ]
}